At the same time, I know that even though I had not had it, I would have had a great welcome.
For my absolute closest friends today is not, that person is still a close friend,
But it is not the person I plug with.
- My friends had heard so much about Örebro
About student life, how welded and welcoming the city is.
Then it was like this, it sounds pretty good.
That's why I chose Örebro.
- Klara and I know each other since before.
You started plugging a little before me.
Me and another friend have been and greeted you a couple of times before we started plugging here.
We thought it was a lot of fun.
Got to go to a nightclub in Örebro City.
Very funny!
- I applied for all medical programs in Sweden and entered Örebro.
- Correct!
- That's why it became Örebro.
- Congratulations!
- It was as good as any.
- How good!
- I haven't bought bus tickets since I moved here.
- boast, boast, boast.
Haha, no but it's really nice as well.
- Yes, I have saved money on it because it is so cheap.
- How do you get around, do you cycle?
- No, or ...
My bike is either twisted or gone, or not as much away as ...
When I moved it was winter and I am not super sharp at cycling.
I thought I won't cycle right now.
So I leave this and pick it up soon.
Then they tore that house!
Did they tore the bike?
Maybe maybe not.
Does anyone have turned the bike?